My brother speaks very well.
What are you going to be when you grow up?
scammer
What?
I became the best cheater
I'm going to make a lot of money
more than you can imagine
Cheaters are bad people
with us
What is the difference with the people who live over there?
But you're trying to be a fraud
It's not just about money
If you become the best scammer
'Cause you can live a fake life like it's real
You're suddenly using sign language
You only do that when you curse at me, right?
- Oh, no.
- I can't do it.
Teach me sign language starting today
Um...
If you run home happily,
ok
Hold on tight
- Wow
- I'm going to run.
Oh!
mister! Wait, wait, stop, stop!
Boy, man, really
Do you know what kind of person I am, yes?
Oh, really
It's too much
Now, now, now, now, now
Hey, I'm a diabetic.
No, if you run out of sugar while driving
Just move on, okay?
Uh, scab
Ah, this is a bit, yeah
child, thank you
Oh, right, there
This as a thank you
Because of the Kim Young-ran Act, it is small.
With sincerity of heart and mind
Ho! oh
Hoo!
what?
Wow
Our Team Leader Han, what’s going on?
Snooping around the private loan market in Myeongdong
To this city administration bastard
Please make all the calls, okay?
Unless you're driving, use both hands.
I have to answer the phone politely.
Sorry for the bluetooth
Well, that's a trivial thing to say
Put it away
Because I received a report about counterfeit money.
Free all year round
Senior, take a look
What?
Counterfeit money report?
Wow, Mr.
Strong teams!
You guys are a little out of it, come back later! Mr.
Brother
Menopause? Why are you so annoyed all of a sudden?
Boy, the smell of alcohol, Mr. Lee
Hey, the alley is narrow, Mr.
Just wait until the boss comes.
You know, my boss personality.
Oh, okay, okay, hey, did you film everything?
Wow
Please get out of the way
Please get out of the way!
Hey
In the wallet
I got my ID card
Hey, what was your name?
- I know this guy.
- Oh, really?
Anything special?
I was biting this
I have some cash to spend.
I kept it in the safe.
It's not fake money, is it?
Oh, the tip line is a prank call, right?
No, against the National Intelligence Service.
Where are you making prank calls?
Is that easy?
Yes, somehow
- Drink only expensive wines
- I charm
When paying millions of won in cash
I should have known about it then.
Tsk
What is this, is it real, what is it, Mr.
Is it real money?
Hey
Which artist's work is this?
Not only a counterfeit detector
infrared detector
to chemical reaction testing
I had a hard time passing it all
Moreover
Because it even has intaglio printing.
Is it a supernote?
To inspect just one piece
Because it took 2 weeks
Back Super Note Paper
It's not the time to be like this, you've had a hard time
Oh, wait a minute.
Don't you remember this counterfeit $100 bill?
That one from the casino counterfeit incident five years ago?
yes
The guy who was shot and killed in Jongno two weeks ago
He said he had this in his mouth.
Intaglio printing just didn't work.
anti-counterfeit device
It was a perfect counterfeit bill.
Unless you look at it from an expert's perspective
How can I see this
I suspected it was counterfeit money.
Did you request a diagnosis?
Who commissioned it?
He's the head of the Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency's powerful team, and his name is...
You said Jang Jung-hyuk, I guess?
It feels cheap?
Do you know each other?
today
can you prove it
We are these two men
I've been waiting for the showdown
Tonight's jackpot is
Who will it explode from?
The finale of today's game
main event
Player entry!
Hey!
Ma, I like upper, upper, Algiers?
Ah, team leader
Did you know there is a crackdown next week?
Yes, brother
Simai Hamo, Gyeonggi Province
Let's tell the guests
Ka, Ma these days, it's so peaceful
Isn’t it all thanks to big brother?
Everything is written
The great monk is holding on just fine.
What's going on?
you want
Place a bet on a player
last chance to get rich
'It's surprise time!'
이 건달 인생은 자고로
굴곡으로 점철돼가
'파란만장', '진퇴양난'
'풍전등화', '위기일발'
'질풍노도'처럼 살아야 되는 거야
형님, '질풍노도'는
청소년 시기를 말하는 건데요
시정하겠습니다
자고로
그, 상대방 말 자르는 새끼들은
혓바닥을 확 잡아
잘라 삐야 되는 기라
확, 고마, 썅놈이
죄송합니다, 시정하겠습니다
누님!
Wow, little brother!
Nice to meet you
I got it
Atta, ma, ma, I got it
What did you do to your face? You've become prettier
Oh, I'm always pretty, why?
- I'll get you a drink.
- Yeah.
Come on, come on, come on, wait a minute
Oh, I just got a phone call.
Hey, hurry and get it.
Yes, brother
yes, i understand
yes
Oh, be careful, be careful
I brought you
- Joong-ki.
- Yes, brother.
You bring some of this.
Did you win some money?
What
I lost everything
Ah, come out
After
Clean up after the game well.
Don't lose, outside
I'll be waiting, bro.
Am I a bastard or a gangster?
Have the kids stand outside the door?
Write, ha
Good
Now
What is it, brother?
Oh no
At the Bank of Manila, Philippines
counterfeit 100 dollar bill
As millions of copies were discovered
the US government
There was a time when I was shocked
At that time, the banknotes were
Indistinguishable from pneumoconiosis
It turned out to be a complete counterfeit bill.
The United States has counterfeit money
We named it ‘Supernote’.
Still
Then this 50,000 won note
Is this a supernote?
yes
What is the basis?
Even those counterfeit bills back then
And that 50,000 won note
Directly from the intaglio printer
I mean, I took a picture of it.
Intaglio printing presses can be found anywhere in the world.
managed by the state
The design is also a confidential document.
It is thoroughly protected.
No, how do you use an intaglio printing machine?
Are you saying you turned it around?
7 years ago in North Korea
Intaglio printing machine blueprint
There was intelligence that it had disappeared.
If it has flowed into the country
It's not impossible.
Is there anyone who can tell?
The guy who made this
$30 million five years ago
Do you remember the casino counterfeit money incident?
100 dollars as evidence at the time and
Jongro shooting incident two weeks ago
This 100 dollars found at the scene
It's the same counterfeit bill.
Coincidentally
50,000 won counterfeit bill
The day the report came in
Jongro shooting incident
was in the mouth of the deceased
When was this $100 found?
It matches exactly
In conclusion
Casino counterfeit money incident
All of this Supernote incident
It is highly likely that it was the same crime.
As a head of a financial crime team,
Let me tell you...
Same criminal...
Now
Report of counterfeit 50,000 won bill received
This is a CCTV photo of a wine bar.
The guy in the picture
At that time, the casino counterfeit money incident
This is the guy named Jay who took the lead.
If Jay had an intaglio printer
If I got it
This counterfeit 100 dollar bill is
It must be Jay's message.
Five years ago, it was the largest in Korea.
The guy who led the counterfeit money incident
Did you bring a supernote this time?
yes
Let's form a team and investigate thoroughly.
Hey, conductor
The counterfeit money incident
This is the responsibility of a dedicated financial crime team.
Isn’t he an expert in that field?
And once in the past
I also have a history of missing out.
I'm going to catch him
I've been going crazy for a few years
There will be a lot of data
Ah, monitoring the private bond market.
To one informant
- Such an important event...
- If you look at sports
director, general manager
Well, isn’t there a system like this?
We also applied that
Mark is in charge of Ki-tae's case.
Yongsan, you are reporting to him.
Let's go to that system
It's a crisis situation.
Okay
fish oil
After wandering around the private bond market,
The skill of frying corn
You've grown a lot, huh?
While gently scratching
Did you really captivate the conductor?
huh?
Did you see that, me?
thank you
Mr. Lee
an accidental incident
- Huh?
- I think it's a ploy to ask the right questions and get reinstated.
Let's see if it goes according to plan.
It's not even the position of Director of the National Intelligence Service, huh?
That's because I covet the team leader position.
What am I doing?
Tsk, don't worry.
The kind of person who dwells on such a small place.
I'm not a petty guy, so let's go.
Ha, uh
Where?
Ha, okay, I'll go there.
D-day flag planting day
It was that day
Suddenly he died
We are also in a difficult situation.
The D-Day flag
Clearance operation, what is that about?
yes
IC
It kills performance
Everyone is only looking for that product.
Can't we buy it?
Developers distribute domestically
I'm not really interested
So?
Are you saying they don’t sell it domestically at all?
They only accept orders worth over 50 billion won.
what? 50 billion?
No matter how good the performance is,
He's so crazy, haha
The crazy one is Mr. Lee.
I'm on this floor
So that I can take a saw
You are the chairman who became a stepping stone.
That prestigious university there
Uh, where is it in the distance?
We took several chemical engineers with us.
Created through repeated research
It's a masterpiece, that sample
If you know each other so well
Oppa, try using your strength.
Wouldn't I have done it?
Brother
Jay...
- Have you heard the name?
- Jay?
Ah
Well, there are a lot of rumors
Anyone who saw it properly
That Jay who says no one is there?
Jay?
yes
Yeah, why?
He says he even pays for the stake?
Jay is in the medicine
I plan to invest 50 billion won
They say there is
So?
It really was through a guy called Fixer.
Of Jay's investment of 50 billion won,
With 25 billion won as advance fee
I received a call saying he would show up.
Laundering counterfeit currency with drugs?
Wow
There are so many, oh so scary
Let's go
follow along
The guy in the car looks like Jay.
Sign the contract right away
Tell them to make a deal.
Ana, when did you see it?
Why do you speak informally like this?
my brother
You are a very careful person.
Tell them you don't work hastily.
The contract location will be contacted later.
Yeah, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute
I'm a bit cautious
Rumor has it that Jay was involved in the counterfeit money incident.
I heard you have experience in conducting.
Is all this money real or counterfeit?
We need to feel it too
Maybe we can make a deal?
Hey, you're annoying, Mr.
IC
Hey
The day Jay and Choi Do-sik signed a contract.
As the appointment location changes in real time
I lost him near Jongno.
Bang bang, bang bang
Tang
Who knew that four months would come?
Jay and the gang
Riding on a truck worth 25 billion won
The place where I met Choi Do-sik
Where did you say it was?
Incheon Port Logistics Warehouse Complex
It's a dock nearby.
I found the location of Jay's hideout.
The hideout I made 5 years ago
I think I'm using it as is
Take the kids right now
Come to Incheon Container Terminal
I joined there
Let’s go hit that guy’s hideout.
Are you ordering me now?
I'm giving you a report.
Yes? Can you hear me?
take the kids
Please come carefully and diligently.
This is what I'm asking you to do
Team leader Yongsan Han!
I'm going to catch you!
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Going to Incheon
Everyone listen carefully
Be alert.
Because he's an incredibly newbie.
yes
Let's take a look
Jay the guy
What a quirky guy he is
Hey, huh?
For a return ceremony after 5 years,
Isn't it too big?
yes?
I'm surprised
Ha, surprise, Mr.
It's been a while since I left here
Hey
Uh, no
Just traces of people
Supernote at the warehouse
The senior's reasoning that he made it
That
Isn't that brave and reckless?
yes?
No...
Yoongyuya
-Who...
- Hey, it's Park Yun-gyu.
It's me, it's me Jeong Sang-gi
Jeong... No, I, I have that name...
Hey, hey, how have you been?
That's enough
I heard that Han Soo-hyun lived and died?
huh?
Hey
It's not a face that came back from the dead, huh?
It's just tight
Well, no, but
Because of you, I took off my team leader clothes.
I was demoted 5 years ago.
How did you get younger?
Okay, that's it.
Don't be soggy
Let's just get to the point, quickly.
Look at me, look at me
'Cause you're such a dirty talker
Containers falling from the sky
I'm just saying that
True
What have you been doing all this time?
Not ‘What did you do for a living?’
I should ask who you met?
You met that bastard?
yes
Jay
He appeared again
As expected
Supernote 2 weeks ago
A distribution report has been received.
same day
you made 5 years ago
A counterfeit $100 bill was discovered.
But today
This is how you came to me on your own
Is it a coincidence?
The counterfeit money incident 5 years ago
people involved
They reappear one by one
me
you
Jay
Jang Jung-hyuk
Even the dead Choi Do-sik
Yes, Choi Do-sik
Ha, in the mouth of Choi Do-sik
100 dollar bite
He must be planning it.
Choi Do-sik’s new identity has never been revealed?
Same goes for $100.
How did you know?
Because I know too much
I guess that's why they want to kill me
What kind of mess is this?
person, person, person
119, 119...
Hey, hey
Are you okay?
Because I almost died
I wanted to live
So I came to see Team Leader Cha.
The only safe area is here
I feel like there isn't one
5 years ago it was 100 dollars
Counterfeit money too
It was so amazing
Now up to 50,000 won
You really mastered it?
This time too, Jay and you
We did it together, right?
That's right
It's my work
Ha, indeed
I couldn't believe it, but haha
all the time in the cell
Master Yang is taking revenge.
I think I was preparing for it.
Soohyun Han
How did Supernote start?
How far have you progressed?
What if I say it?
If I tell you, will you protect me?
Will you protect my life?
Of course
Of course, it is the duty of state institutions.
But if
What if it becomes like it was 5 years ago?
Ha, yeah
Even if it's like 5 years ago
What I believe right now
Because it's just Team Leader Cha.
I'll tell you
Everything
Shall we get started soon?
Supernote game